<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
	<title> - tildes</title>
	<link href="https://aphoenix.ca/tags/tildes/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/>
  <link href="https://aphoenix.ca"/>
	<generator uri="https://www.getzola.org/">Zola</generator>
	<updated>2020-04-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
	<id>https://aphoenix.ca/tags/tildes/atom.xml</id>
	<entry xml:lang="en">
		<title>Game Backlog Burner - Part 4</title>
		<published>2020-04-29T00:00:00+00:00</published>
		<updated>2020-04-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
		<link href="https://aphoenix.ca/blog/game-backlog-burner-4/" type="text/html"/>
		<id>https://aphoenix.ca/blog/game-backlog-burner-4/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I didn&#x27;t have any particular plans for this week, as I had met my goal by week 3. I didn&#x27;t play as much and I revisited
one of the games that I had played in Week 3 - Truberbrook - to make some more progress. Guild of Dungeoneering and 
Q.U.B.E. Director&#x27;s Cut both get mini-reviews.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;span id=&quot;continue-reading&quot;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;h2 id=&quot;week-4&quot;&gt;Week 4&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;q-u-b-e-director-s-cut&quot;&gt;Q.U.B.E. Director&#x27;s Cut&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a cute little puzzler similar to Portal. I really enjoyed it, and I will probably try some of the &amp;quot;extra&amp;quot; stuff 
that is included later, but I&#x27;m probably going to move on to Q.U.B.E. 2 first. This was a very enjoyable 3D puzzle game.
&lt;em&gt;7&#x2F;10&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;guild-of-dungeoneering&quot;&gt;Guild of Dungeoneering&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After playing Book of Demons (4&#x2F;10 do not recommend) I really wanted to play something that scratched the desire I 
didn&#x27;t know that I had which was a dungeon crawly card mechanic game. This is the game that I wanted. It&#x27;s an actual 
card game, with three main phases - you build your guild with items to recruit guild members; you send guild members 
into dungeons, where you place tiles, monsters and loot; you battle monsters that you meet along the way. The graphics 
are adorable, the music is fun, the writing is endearing, the mechanics are good, the card playing is simple, but not so 
simple that it&#x27;s unenjoyable. This probably got bonus marks for scratching in itch awoken by an earlier bad game. &lt;em&gt;8&#x2F;10&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;dandara-trials-of-fear&quot;&gt;Dandara: Trials of Fear&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This one was actually a really impressive game. It&#x27;s one I may come back to in the future to give another shot. It 
reminds me of Celeste in terms of its artwork and presentation and VVVVVV in its gameplay. Your main character can 
launch from surface to surface, sticking only to specifically identified areas of levels. It uses this main mechanic 
and sprawling level design to create a metroidvania with a very unique traversal method. I found that I loved the 
concept and execution of the game (it&#x27;s very well made) but didn&#x27;t love the gameplay itself. I also found it hard to 
mentally map the game and kept getting lost, even in the early areas. &lt;em&gt;6&#x2F;10&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;truberbrook&quot;&gt;Truberbrook&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I played more of Truberbrook - it&#x27;s still fun. I didn&#x27;t spend as much time on games this week as previous weeks; I 
picked up &amp;quot;Drawing on the Right Side of the Brain&amp;quot; and have been working on that in my free time instead.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;final-thoughts&quot;&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My overall goal was to play a game from each of the last 12 Humble Monthly Bundles, and I did that. I also took the 
opportunity to make a library of all the extra keys that I had, but I unfortunately distributed them right before we had 
an event to distribute keys around people. I also spent a bit of time evaluating if I was going to continue with the 
humble monthly bundle, and I will be for now. That bit of retrospection was a nice side effect of this.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was a rough month for me personally - lockdown is starting to grate on me and my family. This event was helpful; 
it was a very enjoyable distraction from the current situation. There were a few standout games - Evergarden is one 
that I&#x27;ve returned to for 10 minutes at a time, and I really like Nordheim and am planning to return to that. I really 
enjoyed this and would take part in another one.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	<entry xml:lang="en">
		<title>Game Backlog Burner - Part 3</title>
		<published>2020-04-22T00:00:00+00:00</published>
		<updated>2020-04-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
		<link href="https://aphoenix.ca/blog/game-backlog-burner-3/" type="text/html"/>
		<id>https://aphoenix.ca/blog/game-backlog-burner-3/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I&#x27;ve thought more on the games since my edits to last week&#x27;s threads. This last week was a bit rough, and I spent more 
time in the evening playing video games than I should have. As a result, I have made it through my April goal, which was 
to play one game from each of the last 12 months of Humble Monthly Bundles. This was one of the best weeks - Evergarden,
Soul Calibur VI, Truberbrook, and a couple of others.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;span id=&quot;continue-reading&quot;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;h2 id=&quot;week-3&quot;&gt;Week 3&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;evergarden-november-2019&quot;&gt;Evergarden &lt;em&gt;November 2019&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a beautiful puzzle game. that I would describe as a cross between the Witness and 2048. You tend a magical 
garden, combining plants to grow them, similar to how you combine numbers in 2048. Plants can have between 1 and 6 
leaves, and combining two 6-leaf plants will allow you to harvest a puzzle piece at the end of the game, which you use 
to solve another type of tile puzzle. It is simple, beautiful, and enticing. I showed to my 9 year old and she played 
one game and beat my high score. I definitely recommend if you enjoy small, self contained puzzle games. &lt;em&gt;8&#x2F;10&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;soul-calibur-vi-december-2019&quot;&gt;Soul Calibur VI &lt;em&gt;December 2019&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a fighting game, which is not really to my taste, but it&#x27;s a &lt;em&gt;pretty good&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; fighting game. Instead of playing 
Story Mode, I started playing Mission mode - in this mode, you create a character and run through... a story. It should 
really be &amp;quot;story&amp;quot; mode. I found the dialog and story more engaging here than in the &amp;quot;Story&amp;quot; mode. Character creation and 
editing is addictive and entertaining. My current fighter is an 8 foot tall living statue that uses enormous zweihander 
swords to fight. I put a few more hours into it beyond my previous update, and I will play Mission mode through to 
completion. I definitely recommend this if you like this sort of game. &lt;em&gt;8&#x2F;10&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;book-of-demons-february-2020&quot;&gt;Book of Demons &lt;em&gt;February 2020&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a sort of rogue-like game that has a couple of sort of card mechanics and it&#x27;s sort of on rails and sort of 
diablo-esque. The graphic style is very cool, very jagged and a bit stylized. There are a bunch of different monsters, 
and I think that there&#x27;s a lot of good individual elements, but you probably noticed how &amp;quot;sort of&amp;quot; everything was. It 
felt disjointed, and I won&#x27;t be returning to it. The cards don&#x27;t make much sense - there&#x27;s no reason for them to be 
cards - the rogue-like elements don&#x27;t make sense when you&#x27;re on a rail, and the game mechanics aren&#x27;t that great, again 
because you&#x27;re on a rail and can&#x27;t move freely. The best thing about it is the janky art. I have uninstalled it and will 
not continue. &lt;em&gt;4&#x2F;10&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;truberbrook-april-2020&quot;&gt;Truberbrook &lt;em&gt;April 2020&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to start by saying that I love Day of the Tentacle and Grim Fandango and Full Throttle. If you like those games, 
you&#x27;ll like this game. It is pointy. It is clicky. The art direction is beautiful. The dialog is good. The characters 
are interesting. The story is cool. If you don&#x27;t like the point and click genre, then you won&#x27;t like this, but I dig 
them. Once I&#x27;m done with Soul Calibur, I will be going back to this: &lt;em&gt;7&#x2F;10&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;niffelheim-march-2020&quot;&gt;Niffelheim &lt;em&gt;March 2020&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I specifically said I would opt for a non-viking based game, and yet here we are. Side note: for a while in university, 
my nickname was actually &amp;quot;Viking&amp;quot;. Amusingly, none of the viking games that I installed and tried are the same genre - 
this is a 2D sidescrolling game that features crafting, gathering, combat, RPG-ish progression, diplomacy, quests... 
there&#x27;s a lot packed in. The art is pretty cool, though I would not call it polished; there&#x27;s an almost &amp;quot;paper cut out&amp;quot; 
quality to it that is endearing if not beautiful. I played for a few hours, and I&#x27;ll come back to this at some point, 
but it&#x27;s not got the same draw as some of the other on my list. &lt;em&gt;6&#x2F;10&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;bonus-games&quot;&gt;Bonus Games&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since I met my original goal, I played some other games as well.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-short-hike&quot;&gt;A Short Hike&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I installed this and got to the peak. This game is very relaxing and happy. I smiled most of 
the time that I played it. It brought delight into an otherwise not particularly delightful week. The graphics are cute, 
but I had to scale down the window a lot so I didn&#x27;t feel queasy while playing, which is a first for me - the 
pixelation, which is intended, was pretty rough at 4k. I played a bit even after reaching the end of the hike, and by 
that I mean that despite reaching the &#x27;end&#x27; I came back the next day and did some more exploring. I will probably do so 
again. &lt;em&gt;9&#x2F;10&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;opus-magnum-april-2020&quot;&gt;Opus Magnum &lt;em&gt;April 2020&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a cute little puzzle game. You are an alchemist, and you are making machines that have a particular input and 
create a particular output. I found it somewhat similar to Human Resource Machine, but I liked HRM better. The character 
that you play as seemed insufferable to me, which is a very minor nitpick, but it was enough to put a bad taste in my 
mouth. I liked having a histogram of how other people performed, but I felt like it was a bit of a whip to continue 
playing, which I fought against. The puzzle aspects are cool, though. &lt;em&gt;6&#x2F;10&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-deadly-tower-of-monsters&quot;&gt;The Deadly Tower of Monsters&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wouldn&#x27;t typically say this, but this game is an absolute gas! The concept is that the game is a cheesy sci-fi movie, 
and there&#x27;s a constant voice over telling you how they did the things that you&#x27;re doing in the game, and why. The 
controls are fine, the graphics are okay, the story is whatever, but what a concept! &lt;em&gt;7&#x2F;10&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&quot;what-s-next&quot;&gt;What&#x27;s next&lt;&#x2F;h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I installed Pathfinder: Kingmaker. &lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I installed Gris. &lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I already had Dandara: Trials of Fear installed and may try this.&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	<entry xml:lang="en">
		<title>Game Backlog Burner - Part 2</title>
		<published>2020-04-15T00:00:00+00:00</published>
		<updated>2020-04-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
		<link href="https://aphoenix.ca/blog/game-backlog-burner-2/" type="text/html"/>
		<id>https://aphoenix.ca/blog/game-backlog-burner-2/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A week into backlog burner and chill and I have made a lot of progress towards the goal of trying out a bunch of games
that were not on my radar at all before now. This is shaping up to be a fun event, and I will be trying to do more of 
these community created events. Surviving Mars, God&#x27;s Trigger, Sonic Mania, Bad North are all up!&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;span id=&quot;continue-reading&quot;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;h2 id=&quot;week-2&quot;&gt;Week 2&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;surviving-mars-august-2019&quot;&gt;Surviving Mars &lt;em&gt;August 2019&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a city building game on Mars. The point is... to survive, and perhaps flourish! I&#x27;ve played through the 
tutorial, and it&#x27;s fairly in depth, very cool, and pretty well done. I&#x27;m not sure if I&#x27;m going to continue playing; 
while I enjoy a lot of things about it, it&#x27;s feeling like a bit of a misfire to me, but I&#x27;m not sure if that&#x27;s covid 
ennui talking, as nothing is seeming as enjoyable for the last few days. I&#x27;m going to give it another go at some point.
&lt;em&gt;7&#x2F;10&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;god-s-trigger-september-2019&quot;&gt;God&#x27;s Trigger *September 2019&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a slick indie action game where you play as an angel and a demon, switching between characters as needed. In 
some ways it reminded me of No More Heroes; it&#x27;s stylish and violent and dark and sometimes funny. The characters are 
cliche, but they know that they are, the levels are hard, but doable, and it&#x27;s got a cool mechanic. I&#x27;m not good at top 
down shooters where you use the left joystick to move and the right joystick to aim and shoot with triggers, but if that 
sounds like fun for you, then this is a good pick. I probably won&#x27;t play &lt;em&gt;too&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; much more, but I might see if 
people are playing it on twitch or something. &lt;em&gt;8&#x2F;10&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;sonic-mania-october-2019&quot;&gt;Sonic Mania &lt;em&gt;October 2019&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was going to check out Battletech from the same month, but it looks huge and intense and I&#x27;m not sure I&#x27;d ever get 
into it, so I went with Sonic Mania instead. Review: It&#x27;s SONIC. I was instantly 10 years old. &lt;em&gt;9&#x2F;10&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;###Bad North - Jotunn Ediition *January 2020&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OMG I skipped a bunch of months. o_O I found this simple game to be fun. I liked the art, and I felt like the concept 
was pretty solid; you command a small army, defending an island from invaders. You must progress eastwards, and you can 
upgrade your little men to improve their defenses. It&#x27;s kind of like a tower defense, but you can constantly adjust your 
defenses by redeploying on the fly. Fun game, but nothing that grabbed me for the long haul. &lt;em&gt;6&#x2F;10&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#x27;m actually getting to bundles where I&#x27;ve played other games in the bundle. Here&#x27;s a mini-review of those, which I&#x27;m not counting as part of the backlog burning.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;blasphemous-december-2019&quot;&gt;Blasphemous &lt;em&gt;December 2019&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A relatively difficult 2D sidescrolling platformer that is definitely a bit, well, blasphemous. Lots of quasi religious 
symbolism turned on its head, often made profane. The story is a bit lacking - I&#x27;m not clear on why I&#x27;m doing anything - 
but the gameplay is fun and relatively easy to get into. I&#x27;m  probably going to eventually complete this. &lt;em&gt;7&#x2F;10&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;two-point-hospital-january-2020&quot;&gt;Two Point Hospital &lt;em&gt;January 2020&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a &lt;strong&gt;delightful&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; little business simulator &#x2F; city builder. It&#x27;s silly, relatively fast paced, and entertaining. 
Optimizing your hospital is not particularly onerous, and each map has a bit of a wrinkle and introduces things at an 
appropriate pace. Cartoony fun! I&#x27;m still playing this off and on. &lt;em&gt;8&#x2F;10&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;###Planet Coaster &lt;em&gt;March 2020&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I only played for about 20 minutes. It feels like a continuation of Roller Coaster Tycoon, which I enjoyed years ago. 
I will get back to it at some point. I haven&#x27;t played enough to give it a fair score, but I&#x27;ll give it this very 
provisional estimatated score: &lt;em&gt;7&#x2F;10&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;next-steps&quot;&gt;Next Steps&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;November 2019 - I think I&#x27;m going to try Evergarden.&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;December 2019 - Soul Calibur VI is most likely the game for this month.&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;February 2020 - Book of Demons&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;March 2020 - Though March has &lt;em&gt;another&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; viking based game (Niffelheim) I&#x27;m going to opt for a non-viking game; probably My Friend Pedro&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;April 2020 - Tossup! Opus Magnum, This is the Police, Truberbrook, Hitman 2. Which should I pick? Anyone have any ideas?&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	<entry xml:lang="en">
		<title>Game Backlog Burner - Part 1</title>
		<published>2020-04-08T00:00:00+00:00</published>
		<updated>2020-04-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
		<link href="https://aphoenix.ca/blog/game-backlog-burner-1/" type="text/html"/>
		<id>https://aphoenix.ca/blog/game-backlog-burner-1/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;At &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;tildes.net&quot;&gt;Tildes&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; there&#x27;s an event going on called the
&lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;tildes.net&#x2F;%7Egames&#x2F;neh&#x2F;tildes_backlog_burner_event_shrink_your_unplayed_games_list_this_april&quot;&gt;Game Backlog Burner&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;
and I have decided to take part in it. Here&#x27;s the
idea in brief:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know that many of us will be stuck at home for this month, I know that many of us could likely use something to pull
our attention away from the news, and I know that many of us have accumulated quite the to-play list of games. &lt;strong&gt;As
such, I&#x27;m thinking it could be fun for us to tackle those lists together and collectively clean up our clutter! Let&#x27;s
all burn through our backlogs!&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;span id=&quot;continue-reading&quot;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There were instructions for how to remove something from your list, but I took the idea and then kind decided to kind
of do my own thing. I am trying out - not getting through - at least one game from each of the last 12 humble monthly
bundles, and reporting in on them.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;week-1&quot;&gt;Week 1&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;northgard-april-2019&quot;&gt;Northgard &lt;em&gt;April 2019&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a nice little RTS game. You&#x27;re a clan of vikings, and you expand outward in little hexes that can have a limited
number of building in each hex. I haven&#x27;t progressed very far, but I will probably continue to casually play this game.
The first map is fairly easy in story mode, and the story itself is fairly good. I do recommend playing this if you get
it in a bundle or something. &lt;em&gt;9&#x2F;10&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;wandersong-may-2019&quot;&gt;Wandersong &lt;em&gt;May 2019&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a cute platformer that I played for half an hour and then deleted. It&#x27;s a cool concept, but there are better
sidescrolling platform games. &lt;em&gt;5&#x2F;10&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;911-operator-june-2019&quot;&gt;911 Operator &lt;em&gt;June 2019&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You play as a 911 Operator; you have to route police officers, paramedics, and firemen to different calls that you
receive. When I logged in, it offered to put me in my home city, which was kind of cool. It doesn&#x27;t seem particularly
difficult on start, but I sense that it could get pretty hectic pretty quickly. I found it enjoyable; I&#x27;ll probably
casually play it, but I don&#x27;t know how in-depth I&#x27;d go with it. Cool concept, graphics are simple but effective, giving
me a home map felt cool. &lt;em&gt;7&#x2F;10&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;love-is-dead-july-2019&quot;&gt;Love is Dead &lt;em&gt;July 2019&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is the apocalypse; you are a zombie. Everyone is a zombie! You must reunite with your lover (a zombie) and find your
pets (guess what, zombies). Each level is a puzzle where you have to find how to get to your lover. The puzzles haven&#x27;t
gotten particularly difficult, but there&#x27;s extra items to find in each one. The graphics are simple, the controls are
very easy, the story is sweet. I will probably play this one or two more times. &lt;em&gt;6&#x2F;10&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#x27;m 1&#x2F;3 of the way through my goal, so this should be a cakewalk. ;)&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
</feed>
