<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
	<title> - rock</title>
	<link href="https://aphoenix.ca/tags/rock/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/>
  <link href="https://aphoenix.ca"/>
	<generator uri="https://www.getzola.org/">Zola</generator>
	<updated>2007-03-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
	<id>https://aphoenix.ca/tags/rock/atom.xml</id>
	<entry xml:lang="en">
		<title>5✭ Fridays - The Creepshow</title>
		<published>2007-03-16T00:00:00+00:00</published>
		<updated>2007-03-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
		<link href="https://aphoenix.ca/blog/5-fridays-the-creepshow/" type="text/html"/>
		<id>https://aphoenix.ca/blog/5-fridays-the-creepshow/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It&#x27;s been a while since I&#x27;ve been able to write about music for a variety of reasons. First there&#x27;s the whole music 
player scandal, which is still bothering me quite a bit. There are no clear winners thus far, only clear losers. The 
only thing that&#x27;s keeping me going is Pandora, but it&#x27;s got a bit of a problem in that I can&#x27;t just select whatever song
I&#x27;m jonesing to hear. So, once again, no music from my library. Problem the second: I&#x27;ve had the plague. It wasn&#x27;t too 
bad - sore throat, coughing, boils, rain of toads and the like - but I&#x27;ve been spending most of my time abed and not 
listening to music or thinking about writing. When I got back from being sick, my time was spent equally between 
catching up on 150 email messages and being excited about being able to go see (and open for) the Creepshow.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;span id=&quot;continue-reading&quot;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First off, let&#x27;s talk about bass players. I play bass, and I play it very well, but I don&#x27;t &lt;em&gt;have&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; a double bass, so I&#x27;m
already behind Sickboy from the Creepshow. He&#x27;s got a great big black double bass with a skull on it, and he plays it 
about as well as I&#x27;ve ever seen one played. And I&#x27;ve seen Jim Creegan multiple times as well as the Reverend Horton 
Heat&#x27;s bass player, and they&#x27;re both amazing. Sickboy&#x27;s a little better, possibly because of his pork pie hat and jazz 
shoes, or possibly because sometimes his hands moved so fast I couldn&#x27;t see them.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reverend Ginty plays keys and sings and looks like he&#x27;s going about 160 miles per hour. His organ skills are very slick,
and every once in a while he breaks into one of those hockey-game organ bits where everyone yells &amp;quot;Charge!&amp;quot; It&#x27;s wildly 
entertaining.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Matt Pomade is an intensely good drummer. He plays a simple four-piece kit with a high hat, crash and a ride and that&#x27;s 
it. My sentiments can be summed up by the observation of one of my co-enthralled friends: &amp;quot;That dude ain&#x27;t human.&amp;quot; I&#x27;ve 
rarely seen drummers move as fast as he does or do so much with so little.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, I&#x27;d been looking forward to meeting Hellcat, the lead singer of the band, but I was informed shortly before 
arriving at the gig, that Hellcat has got herself in a family way (congrats to her in June) and she has been replaced 
for the nonce by her younger sister, Sarah.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;rock&#x2F;TheCreepshow.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The Creepshow at Wilf&#x27;s.  Photo courtesy of Sean Yo.&quot; &#x2F;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sarah is a tiny, tiny little blonde girl. She&#x27;s five feet tall, and maybe 95 pounds. She is exquisitely beautiful and 
somewhat frail looking. I must be honest and say that I was at first a little disappointed - she was not what I was 
expecting - but then she took the stage, and boy did she ever take the stage. She&#x27;s got a powerful voice and plays a 
great big blue Schecter Corsair hollowbody guitar that&#x27;s about as big as she is, and she plays it exceptionally well. 
Her greatest asset, though, is her stage presence. She easily has the best mass-to-stage-presence ratio of anyone I&#x27;ve 
ever had the luck to see.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, the band was exceptionally tight, with lots of great hooks - bass solos, organ solos, lots of crowd 
participation, exhortations to the crowd to start dancing and more. They&#x27;re a great mix of swing, horrorpunk (à la 
Misfits) and rockabilly, and I can&#x27;t wait to see them play again. If you get the chance, and you don&#x27;t mind the idea of 
a swing song about &lt;em&gt;Des Vampyrs&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; then you should certainly check out The Creepshow.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	<entry xml:lang="en">
		<title>5✭ Fridays - Tool</title>
		<published>2007-02-09T00:00:00+00:00</published>
		<updated>2007-02-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
		<link href="https://aphoenix.ca/blog/5-fridays-tool/" type="text/html"/>
		<id>https://aphoenix.ca/blog/5-fridays-tool/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Time passes and I have not yet finished my ongoing evaluation of music players (the race is close between WinAmp and 
Windows Media Player, of all things. iTunes is right out, again). As a result, I cannot turn to a random 5✭ song and 
expound at length about song and artist, which is my normal modus operandi for these articles. Instead, we shall explore 
in some detail one of my favourite bands of all time; Tool. Once again, a caveat: you may find Tool to be strangely 
offputting and discomforting, and you may find them to be wildly offensive; they may just get you thinking, though, and 
that&#x27;s quite the accomplishment in the MTV age. And another caveat: any information here may be inaccurate, since Tool 
is notorious for spreading (often hilarious) misinformation about themselves.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;span id=&quot;continue-reading&quot;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is difficult to know where to start when discussing Tool. They are often categorized as &lt;em&gt;progressive rock&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; which is 
code for &lt;em&gt;very difficult to classify&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;. They are most certainly a rock band with a fairly standard set up; a guitarist, 
a bassist, a drummer and a singer. They definitely fall more towards the &lt;em&gt;heavy&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; end of the spectrum, and one would also 
classify them as &lt;em&gt;experimental&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;. Other words that come to mind are &lt;em&gt;strange, angry, difficult,&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;intense&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maynard James Keenan is the singer &#x2F; lyricist of the band, and his powerful and unique voice is probably the first thing 
you&#x27;ll notice. Maynard&#x27;s voice ranges from sweet to dark to screaming; the fifth track from &lt;em&gt;Opiate&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; features one of the 
most intense and bonechilling screams I have ever heard from a human voice, but &amp;quot;The Pot&amp;quot; from &lt;em&gt;10,000 Days&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; is started 
in a sweet, moderate tenor. His subject matter channels anger from many sources - disaffectation from religion, 
childhood trauma, hypocrisy of media and politicians, etc - and may make you squirm on hearing them. For instance, 
&amp;quot;Prison Sex&amp;quot; from the album &lt;em&gt;Undertow&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; talks in detail about acts of abuse to children, and how abuse begets abuse. It 
is not an easy song to listen to.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adam Jones is Tool&#x27;s guitarist and is also the artist behind many of their videos. He&#x27;s classically trained in string 
instruments, and taught himself to play guitar, learning by ear. Jones is one of those elusive animals that often fail 
to get their due recognition: a fantastic rhythm guitarist. You are not likely to hear any blistering guitar solos in 
his work, but he has such an amazing sense of timing and harmony that you may be surprised that there aren&#x27;t more 
guitars playing. Although, sometimes, what you&#x27;re hearing is actually Tool&#x27;s bass player, Justin Chancellor.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chancellor frequently plays bass as if he were actually a lead guitar player, and I would be remiss if I didn&#x27;t say that 
he is one of my personal main sources of inspration in how I play bass guitar. The interplay of Chancellor&#x27;s bass with 
Jones&#x27; guitar is one of the keys to the unique sound of Tool; the two are so &lt;em&gt;tight&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; that it seems as if they play with 
one mind together. Chancellor&#x27;s bass riff in &amp;quot;Forty Six &amp;amp; 2&amp;quot; from the album &lt;em&gt;Ænima&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; is a fantastic, percussive riff that 
is one of the best examples of his ability to grab the reigns in a song, which is extraordinairily hard to do when one 
of your band mates is Danny Carey.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Danny Carey is where my essay is going to fall apart, because I really can&#x27;t tell you much about him. It&#x27;s possible that 
he thinks of drumming as an occult experience. It&#x27;s possible that he thinks he has summoned and contained a demon, which 
makes it possible for him to do what he does. It&#x27;s possible that he&#x27;s just a great drummer that started off learning 
jazz and then took the polyrhythmic bebop that he had learned and applied it to rock. It&#x27;s possible that he&#x27;s the 
greatest drummer of our time. The greatest single act of technical instrument mastery that I have ever heard was a Danny 
Carey drum solo, during which he sustained rhythms in at least 4 identifiable non-multiplicable time signatures (a 
3-4-5-7 polyrhythm†), and somehow let the polyrhythm dissolve into a pattern that was recognizable as the beginning to 
one of Tool&#x27;s songs. I was thoroughly dumbfounded.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tool is made up of four musicians who individually are among the best at their instruments. Together, they create a 
whole that is disturbing and strange, often very primal, angry and interesting. Their live show is among the best that 
I&#x27;ve seen; one time they incorporated gymnasts who performed à la Cirque de Soleil.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#x27;s also interesting to note that quite a few classical musicians are interested in Tool. There have been at least two 
String Quartet tribute albums to tool, wherin Tool is arranged and performed by string instruments, without percussion. 
It certainly highlights how the most important aspect of their music is rhythm.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best Tool album is &lt;em&gt;Ænima&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;, so if you have never heard Tool, start there. You could also listen to &lt;em&gt;Lateralus&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; and 
try to tap your foot along to &amp;quot;Schism.&amp;quot; You may end up with the strange problem that the music makes you want to move 
your body, but confounds your feet. And keep an open mind - you may learn something.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;† - I&#x27;ll try to explain: music is made up of small units called &amp;quot;measures&amp;quot; which have a certain length according to the 
number of beats. Rock music frequently has 4 beats in a measure; a waltz normally has 3. A polyrhythm is playing two 
measures at the same time, of the same length, that have a different number of beats in them; you end up with beats 
crossing and being played in and around each other. Carey played 3, 4, 5 and 7 beat measures all at the same time, which 
means that each hand and each foot were all tapping at slightly different paces. To get an idea of how difficult this 
is, try tapping your right foot and left hand at consistent speeds that are not the same. Or set 2 metronomes to 
different speeds, and try to tap along with both of them.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	<entry xml:lang="en">
		<title>5✭ Fridays - The Misfits</title>
		<published>2007-01-26T00:00:00+00:00</published>
		<updated>2007-01-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
		<link href="https://aphoenix.ca/blog/5-fridays-the-misfits/" type="text/html"/>
		<id>https://aphoenix.ca/blog/5-fridays-the-misfits/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;One of my favourite blogs to read is &lt;a href=&quot;http:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.tbray.org&#x2F;ongoing&#x2F;&quot;&gt;Tim Bray&#x27;s Ongoing&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; - and this is a funny lead in 
to my first music post, because Tim is very much a technophile (for instance, he was recently &lt;a href=&quot;http:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.linuxjournal.com&#x2F;issue&#x2F;151&quot;&gt;featured on the cover of 
Linux Journal&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;, and on the inside too!). One of my favourite recurring themes is 
his &amp;quot;5✭♫&amp;quot; posts, in which he expounds on various musics that he listens to.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the title looks broken, you should &lt;a href=&quot;http:&#x2F;&#x2F;tools.google.com&#x2F;firefox&#x2F;toolbar&#x2F;bundle&#x2F;&quot;&gt;Get Firefox&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;. It&#x27;s the simplest 
way to fix it.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;span id=&quot;continue-reading&quot;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, in the spirit of thievery Open Source Ideas, I&#x27;m going to implement something similar. Right now it&#x27;s called &amp;quot;5✭ 
Fridays&amp;quot; and I&#x27;m going to tell you a bit about what I&#x27;m listening to... and at this moment it&#x27;s the Misfits (warning: 
the Misfits may be offensive).&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;rock&#x2F;TheMisfits.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;A Logo for the Misfits&quot; &#x2F;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Misfits are a great punk band. I&#x27;ll tell you right now that, even though I&#x27;m &lt;em&gt;in&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; a punk band, it&#x27;s not a genre of 
music that I listen to regularly. Punk&#x27;s great, but I tend to want a bit more, um, &lt;em&gt;music&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; in my music. There&#x27;s often a 
wall of sound and some yelling, and lots of double kick drum riffs, and a bass player that rakes the strings constantly, 
and it gets old quick. Also, even though I have a lot of rage, it&#x27;s mostly a quiet, vitriolic, smoldering rage that 
lends itself more to Metal or Franz Liszt. I&#x27;m not &amp;quot;anti-establishment&amp;quot; either; the man&#x27;s not keeping me down and I 
don&#x27;t have a yearning for anarchy. The Misfits carve right through all the problems that I have by using angry but 
harmonic guitars and establishing strong melodic vocals singing B-movie themed lyrics that are as apt to make you laugh 
as to incite anger in you. Here&#x27;s &amp;quot;Resurrection&amp;quot; (beware the mild sacrilege)&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Complications inside of me reminds me that my heart won&#x27;t always 
beat The ugly face of death that&#x27;s smiling at my rotting teeth&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will die here in this sorrow 
I was waiting for tomorrow 
Palpitate the pulse until you 
feel 
my 
heart explode against the wall&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Talk about me, Laugh about me cry about me... nail me to the cross 
I&#x27;ll be a martyr for the hated, the weak, the ugly, the lost&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will die here in this sorrow 
I won&#x27;t wait for tomorrow 
Palpitate the pulse until you 
resurrect 
my 
soul from the wall&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zombie much? To go with this, they have an astoundingly catchy melody and a powerful guitar riff, which is one of the 
most used chord progressions in history - but it works. It&#x27;s got a beat that&#x27;s hard to, well, beat, and it gets my head 
bobbing along every time I hear the song.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Misfits have this tendency to eschew writing lots of lyrics, which may be a biproduct of the fact that their songs 
tend to be under two minutes in length. &amp;quot;Resurrection&amp;quot; runs 1:29 and goes all-out for the duration. Another Misfits song 
that is amongst my favourites is &amp;quot;The Haunting&amp;quot; which clocks in at 1:27 and is basically a 40 second song with a repeat. 
It&#x27;s not a complicated song, but they&#x27;re not a complicated band, and sometimes it&#x27;s not about complication; the gestalt 
is more than the sum of its parts. There are only five chords in &amp;quot;The Haunting&amp;quot;, but they&#x27;re the &lt;em&gt;right&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; five chords, 
and they&#x27;re supported by the powerful melody and the intense energy.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in trying punk out for a spin, but want less noise and more melody, as many people often do, you 
would be hardpressed to find a better package than the Misfits. Besides, if you don&#x27;t like them, the song will be done 
in just a minute.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
</feed>
